<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Wireless Sensor Network</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="email_address">hr@atechindia.com</string>
    <string name="email_address_cc">lakhbir@atechindia.com</string>
    <string name="email_address_bcc">mani@atechindia.com</string>
    <string name="wsn_info">A sensor network is an infrastructure comprised of sensing computing and communication elements that gives an administrator the ability to instrument, observe and react to events and phenomena in a specified environment. The WSN is built of "nodes" – from a few to several hundreds or even thousands, where each node is connected to one (or sometimes several) sensors.</string>
    <string name="wsn_func">We cover wireless sensor network technology, applications, communication techniques, networking protocols, middleware, security, system management. It comprises of nodes which works on network of 2.4GHZ or 865MHZ to the coordinator . This coordinator can send the data through Bluetooth , data can also be send using GSM to mobile via internet or wifi and cloud computing through GPRS.</string>
    <string name="wsn_comp">1.WSN Coordinator( both 2,.4 Ghz and 866 Mhz range ) \n
	   \t  •	Supports various network topologies (star, mesh, tree, bus, ring)\n
\t  •	20*4 LCD display  \n
\t  •	ARM processor \n
\t  •	Other communication modules GSM, Bluetooth, GPRS \n
\t  •	Inbuilt rechargeable battery \n
2. Intelligent end node \n
\t  •	ARM processor \n
\t  •	Supports various network topologies (star, mesh, tree, bus ,ring)\n
\t  •	Internal  battery backup \n
3. Sensors used \n
\t  •	With sensors , like humidity , temp , motion , acceleration \n
different sensors , kin proper packing , weather proof \n
with rechargeable battery back up, enclouser \n
\t  •	Sensors used in body area network such as ECG, EEG, blood pressure , moment sensor and breathing sensor .</string>
    <string name="robocontrol_info">The Robot Car can go anywhere using a robot controller application which give directions to move.</string>
    <string name="robocontrol_func">The Robot Car takes input commands like \'f\' for forward, \'b\' for backword, \'r\' for right rotate, \'l\' for left rotate and \'s\' to stop. </string>
    <string name="robocontrol_comp">Two motors to rotate wheels, Arduino board, Battery, Bluetooth module.</string>
    <string name="robohand_info">The six degrees-of-freedom robotic arm has the equivalent of a shoulder, elbow and wrist, along with a base and a gripper, thereby closely resembling a human arm. The arm can be controlled by rotating the servo motors at each joint.</string>
    <string name="robohand_func">Servo motors are used for precision positioning. The servo motor at each joint of the robotic arm can be controlled by using the sliders given. The values given by the sliders generate a PWM pulse which set the servo motor at the corresponding angle.</string>
    <string name="robohand_comp">Six Servo motors, Arduino board, Bluetooth module.</string>

</resources>